大家好，欢迎来到我们的阅读时间
Hi everyone , welcome to our reading time
这就是码头
This is marina
今天我们要读一读小原则
Today we are going to read the little princ
第一章
Chapter ONE
一次是在我六岁的时候
Once when i was six years old
我在一片嘘声中看到了一张宏伟的画面
I saw a magnificent picture in a boo
来自 natur 的真实故事
Called true stories from natur
关于原初邪恶森林
About the prime evil forest
那是一条蟒蛇的照片
It was a picture of a boa constricto
吞食动物的行为
In the act of swallowing an animal
这是图纸的副本
Here IS A COPY OF THE DRAWING
在嘘声中
In the boo
它说：蟒蛇吞下他们的猎物 whol
It said : boa constrictors swallow their prey whol
无需咀嚼
Without chewing it
之后他们就不能移动了
After that they are not able to move
他们睡过消化所需的六个月
And they sleep through the six months that they need for digestion
我沉思着
I pondered deepl
然后穿越丛林的冒险
Then over the adventures of the jungle
在用彩色铅笔工作一番之后
And after some work with a colored pencil
我成功地画了我的第一幅画
I SUCCEEDED IN MAKING MY FIRST DRAWING
我的第一名
My join number one
它看起来像这样
It looked like this
我向大人们展示了我的杰作
I showed my masterpiece to the grown ups
并问他们这幅画是否吓到了他们
And asked them whether the drawing frightened them
但他们害怕地回答
But they answered frightened
为什么有人应该被帽子吓到
Why SHOULD ANYONE BE FRIGHTENED BY A HAT
我的画不是一顶帽子的图片
My drawing was not a picture of a hat
那是一张蟒蛇消化大象的照片
It WAS A PICTURE OF A BOA CONSTRICTOR DIGESTING AN ELEPHANT
但是由于大人们无法理解它
But since the grown ups were not able to understand it
我又画了一幅画
I made another drawing
我画了 BOA 构造器的内部
I DREW THE INSIDE OF THE BOA CONSTRUCTOR
这样大人们才能看得清楚
So that the grown ups could see it clearly
他们总是需要解释事情
They always need to have things explained
我的第二幅画是这样的
My drawing number two looked like this
这次大人们的反应是劝我
The grown ups response this time was to advise m
放下我对蟒蛇的画作
To lay aside my drawings of boa constrictors
无论是从内部还是从外部
Whether from the inside or the outside
转而致力于地理
And devote myself instead to geography
历史、算术和语法
History , arithmetic and grammar
这就是为什么在六岁时
That is why at the age of six
我放弃了本来可能辉煌的画家生涯
I give up what might have been a magnificent career as a painter
我对我的加入号码失败感到沮丧
I had been disheartened by the failure of my join number on
我的第二个加入
And my join number two
大人自己永远无法理解任何事情
Grown ups never understand anything by themselves
孩子们总是永远向他们解释事情是令人厌烦的
And it is tiresome for children to be always and forever explaining things to them
所以后来我选择了另一个专业
So then i chose another professio
并学习驾驶 airplant
And learn to pilot airplants
我飞遍了世界各地
I have flown a little over all parts of the world
确实，地理对 m 非常有用
And it is true that geography has been very useful to m
一目了然
At a glance
我可以区分中国和亚利松
I can distinguish china from arizon
如果一个人在黑夜迷路
If one gets lost in the night
这些知识很有价值
Such knowledge is valuable
在今生的过程中
In THE COURSE OF THIS LIFE
我遇到过很多次
I have had a great many encounter
与很多人在一起
With A GREAT MANY PEOPLE
谁曾关心过重要的事情
Who have been concerned with matters of consequence
我在成年人中生活了很多
I have lived a great deal among grown ups
我看到他们近在咫尺
I have seen them immediately close at hand
而这种情况并没有因为堆积而得到太大改善
And that hasn't much improved by piling of them
每当我遇到他们中的一个
Whenever i met one of them
在我看来，谁是完全清楚的
Who seemed to me at all clear sided
我尝试了向他展示我的 1 号加入的实验
I tried the experiment of showing him my join number one
我一直保持着
Which i have always kept
我会试着找出答案
I would try to find out
所以，如果这是一个真正有理解力的人
So if this was a person of true understanding
但不管是谁
But whoever it was
他或她总是会说
He or she would always say
那是一顶帽子
That is a hat
那我就永远不会和那个人谈论蟒蛇
Then i would never talk to that person about boa constrictors
或者为邪恶森林或星星
Or prime evil forests or stars
我会把自己降低到他的水平
I would bring myself down to his level
我会和他谈论桥牌和高尔夫，以及政治和领带
I would talk to him about bridge and golf , and politics and neckties
长大后会很高兴遇到这样一个明智的人
And the growing up would be greatly pleased to have met such a sensible man
感谢您的收听
Thank you for listenin
下次我们要读第二章
Next time we are going to read the chapter two
下次再见 再见
See YOU NEXT TIME BYE BYE